// [...document.querySelectorAll("tr.ng-star-inserted")].map(row =>({
//     folder: row.closest(".accordion-container").querySelector("p").textContent,
//     problem:row.querySelector("b").textContent,
//     solution:row.querySelector("a.button.is-rounded.is-info.is-small.is-outlined").href
// }))

module.exports = [
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Contains Duplicate",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/3OamzN90kPg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Valid Anagram",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/9UtInBqnCgA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Two Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KLlXCFG5TnA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Group Anagrams",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vzdNOK2oB2E"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Top K Frequent Elements",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YPTqKIgVk-k"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Product of Array Except Self",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bNvIQI2wAjk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Valid Sudoku",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TjFXEUCMqI8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Encode and Decode Strings",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B1k_sxOSgv8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Arrays & Hashing",
        "problem": "Longest Consecutive Sequence",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P6RZZMu_maU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Two Pointers",
        "problem": "Valid Palindrome",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jJXJ16kPFWg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Two Pointers",
        "problem": "Two Sum II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQ1Oz4ckceM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Two Pointers",
        "problem": "3Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzZsG8n2R9A"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Two Pointers",
        "problem": "Container with Most Water",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UuiTKBwPgAo"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Two Pointers",
        "problem": "Trapping Rain Water",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZI2z5pq0TqA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Best Time to Buy & Sell Stock",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1pkOgXD63yU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Longest Substring Without Repeating Characters",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/wiGpQwVHdE0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Longest Repeating Character Replacement",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/gqXU1UyA8pk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Permutation in String",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UbyhOgBN834"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Minimum Window Substring",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/jSto0O4AJbM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Sliding Window",
        "problem": "Sliding Window Maximum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DfljaUwZsOk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Valid Parentheses",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/WTzjTskDFMg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Min Stack",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qkLl7nAwDPo"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Evaluate Reverse Polish Notation",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/iu0082c4HDE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Generate Parentheses",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s9fokUqJ76A"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Daily Temperatures",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cTBiBSnjO3c"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Car Fleet",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pr6T-3yB9RM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Stack",
        "problem": "Largest Rectangle in Histogram",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zx5Sw9130L0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Binary Search",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s4DPM8ct1pI"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Search a 2D Matrix",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ber2pi2C0j0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Koko Eating Bananas",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U2SozAs9RzA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Search Rotated Sorted Array",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U8XENwh8Oy8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Find Minimum in Rotated Sorted Array",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIVW4P8b1VA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Time Based Key-Value Store",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fu2cD_6E8Hw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Binary Search",
        "problem": "Find Median of Two Sorted Arrays",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q6IEA26hvXc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Reverse Linked List",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G0_I-ZF0S38"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Merge Two Linked Lists",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XIdigk956u0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Reorder List",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S5bfdUTrKLM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Remove Nth Node from End of List",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XVuQxVej6y8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Copy List with Random Pointer",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Y2EiZST97Y"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Add Two Numbers",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wgFPrzTjm7s"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Linked List Cycle",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gBTe7lFR3vc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Find the Duplicate Number",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wjYnzkAhcNk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "LRU Cache",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ABFKPK2hD4&t=858s"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Merge K Sorted Lists",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q5a5OiGbT6Q"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Linked List",
        "problem": "Reverse Nodes in K-Group",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1UOPsfP85V4"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Invert Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OnSn2XEQ4MY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Maximum Depth of Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hTM3phVI6YQ&lc=UgxUajmaDDsmZ5Tp0U54AaABAg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Diameter of a Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bkxqA8Rfv04"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Balanced Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QfJsau0ItOY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Same Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vRbbcKXCxOw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Subtree of Another Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E36O5SWp-LE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Lowest Common Ancestor of a BST",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gs2LMfuOR9k"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Binary Tree Level Order Traversal",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ZnyEApgFYg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Binary Tree Right Side View",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d4zLyf32e3I"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Count Good Nodes in a Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7cp5imvDzl4"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Validate Binary Search Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s6ATEkipzow"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Kth Smallest Element in a BST",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5LUXSvjmGCw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Construct Tree from Preorder and Inorder Traversal",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ihj4IQGZ2zc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Binary Tree Max Path Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hr5cWUld4vU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Trees",
        "problem": "Serialize and Deserialize Binary Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u4JAi2JJhI8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Tries",
        "problem": "Implement Trie",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oobqoCJlHA0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Tries",
        "problem": "Design Add and Search Word Data Structure",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BTf05gs_8iU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Tries",
        "problem": "Word Search II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=asbcE9mZz_U"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Kth Largest Element in a Stream",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hOjcdrqMoQ8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Last Stone Weight",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-QCq79-Vfw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "K Closest Points to Origin",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rI2EBUEMfTk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Kth Largest Element in an Array",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XEmy13g1Qxc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Task Scheduler",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s8p8ukTyA2I"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Design Twitter",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pNichitDD2E"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Heap_Priority Queue",
        "problem": "Find Median from Data Stream",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=itmhHWaHupI"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Subsets",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=REOH22Xwdkk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Combination Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GBKI9VSKdGg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Permutations",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7AvT7cGdSo"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Subsets II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vn2v6ajA7U0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Combination Sum II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rSA3t6BDDwg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Word Search",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pfiQ_PS1g8E"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Palindrome Partitioning",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3jvWodd7ht0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "Letter Combinations of a Phone Number",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0snEunUacZY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Backtracking",
        "problem": "N-Queens",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ph95IHmRp5M"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Number of Islands",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pV2kpPD66nE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Clone Graph",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mQeF6bN8hMk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Max Area of Island",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJGr1OtmH0c"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Pacific Atlantic Waterflow",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s-VkcjHqkGI"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Surrounded Regions",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9z2BunfoZ5Y"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Rotting Oranges",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y704fEOx0s0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Walls and Gates",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e69C6xhiSQE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Course Schedule",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EgI5nU9etnU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Course Schedule II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Akt3glAwyfY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Redundant Connection",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FXWRE67PLL0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Number of Connected Components in Graph",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8f1XPm4WOUc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Graph Valid Tree",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bXsUuownnoQ"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Graphs",
        "problem": "Word Ladder",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h9iTnkgv05E"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Reconstruct Itinerary",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZyB_gQ8vqGA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Min Cost to Connect all Points",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7JOBJIC-NA"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Network Delay Time",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EaphyqKU4PQ"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Swim in Rising Water",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=amvrKlMLuGY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Alien Dictionary",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6kTZYvNNyps"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Advanced Graphs",
        "problem": "Cheapest Flights Within K Stops",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5eIK3zUdYmE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Climbing Stairs",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y0lT9Fck7qI"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Min Cost Climbing Stairs",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ktmzAZWkEZ0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "House Robber",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73r3KWiEvyk"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "House Robber II",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rWAJCfYYOvM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Longest Palindromic Substring",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XYQecbcd6_c"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Palindromic Substrings",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4RACzI5-du8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Decode Ways",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6aEyTjOwlJU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Coin Change",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H9bfqozjoqs"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Maximum Product Subarray",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lXVy6YWFcRM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Word Break",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sx9NNgInc3A"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cjWnW0hdF1Y"
    },
    {
        "folder": "1-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Partition Equal Subset Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IsvocB5BJhw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Unique Paths",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlEsdxuD4lY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Longest Common Subsequence",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ua0GhsJSlWM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Best Time to Buy & Sell Stock With Cooldown",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I7j0F7AHpb8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Coin Change II ",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mjy4hd2xgrs"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Target Sum",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g0npyaQtAQM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Interleaving String",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Rw3p9LrgvE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Longest Increasing Path in a Matrix",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wCc_nd-GiEc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Distinct Subsequences",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-RDzMJ33nx8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Edit Distance",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XYi2-LPrwm4"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Burst Balloons",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VFskby7lUbw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "2-D Dynamic Programming",
        "problem": "Regular Expression Matching",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HAA8mgxlov8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Maximum Subarray",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5WZl3MMT0Eg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Jump Game",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yan0cv2cLy8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Jump Game II ",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dJ7sWiOoK7g"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Gas Station",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lJwbPZGo05A"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Hand of Straights",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=amnrMCVd2YI"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Merge Triplets to Form Target Triplet",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/kShkQLQZ9K4"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Partition Labels",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B7m8UmZE-vw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Greedy",
        "problem": "Valid Parenthesis String",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QhPdNS143Qg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Insert Interval",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/A8NUOmlwOlM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Merge Intervals",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/44H3cEC2fFM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Non-Overlapping Intervals",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/nONCGxWoUfM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Meeting Rooms",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/PaJxqZVPhbg"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Meeting Rooms II",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/FdzJmTCVyJU"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Intervals",
        "problem": "Minimum Interval to Include Each Query",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5hQ5WWW5awQ"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Rotate Image",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fMSJSS7eO1w"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Spiral Matrix",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/BJnMZNwUk1M"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Set Matrix Zeroes",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T41rL0L3Pnw"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Happy Number",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ljz85bxOYJ0"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Plus One",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jIaA8boiG1s"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Pow(x, n)",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g9YQyYi4IQQ"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Multiply Strings",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1vZswirL8Y8"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Math & Geometry",
        "problem": "Detect Squares",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bahebearrDc"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Single Number",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qMPX1AOa83k"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Number of 1 Bits",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/5Km3utixwZs"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Counting Bits",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/RyBM56RIWrM"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Reverse Bits",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/UcoN6UjAI64"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Missing Number",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/WnPLSRLSANE"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Sum of Two Integers",
        "solution": "https://youtu.be/gVUrDV4tZfY"
    },
    {
        "folder": "Bit Manipulation",
        "problem": "Reverse Integer",
        "solution": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HAgLH58IgJQ"
    }
]